## Giang Văn Linh

PHP Developer

☑ linhbq89@gmail.com

0337 229 661

≝ 17/03/2001

• Ho Chi Minh city, VietNam

https://linhgv.name.vn/

## SUMMARY

Graduated from FPT Polytechnic College with a strong passion for web development and amosts 2 years of work experience at Digityze Asia. Proficient in OOP, HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, JavaScript, and Bootstrap 5. Well-versed in PHP (Laravel), MySQL, RESTful APIs, MongoDB, and Photoshop. Possesses basic knowledge of front-end website design using WordPress with Elementor. Experienced in using GIT for source control throughout various projects.

## **TARGET**

I would like to join your team to develop my skills and contribute to complex web projects, optimize system performance. Aim to become an expert in web application development, continuously learn and apply new technologies to meet the growing needs of the industry.

### **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2023

#### **WEBSITE PROGRAMING**

FPT Polytechnic College

Medium score: 7.9

## SKILLS

Programming language: PHP, JavaScript, SQL

Frameworks: Laravel, Codelgniter, VueJS

Database: MySQL, MariaDB, MongoDB

## SHORT SKILLS

- Teamwork skills
- Analytical thinking and problem solving
- Time management and multitasking
- · Ability to self-study and research

Website: HTML, CSS (TailwindCSS, Bootstrap), jQuery, AlpineJS, NodeJS

Tools: Git, GitLab, REST API, OOP, Trigger, Docker

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **DIGITYZE ASIA CO.,LTD**

06/2023 - 09/2024

#### FRESHER PHP DEVELOPER

- Developed and maintained web applications using Laravel and Codelgniter, improving system performance by 80%.
- Collaborated with a cross-functional team to design and implement a human resources management system, handling data for over 2000 employees.
- Deployed efficient database queries with MySQL, reducing query response time by 20%.

#### **Fpoly Software Company**

1/2023 - 4/2023

#### PHP INTERNSHIP

- Executed tasks assigned by the instructor and reported final results for the course.
- Learned and applied PHP and Laravel knowledge to real-world projects.

## **PROJECT**

## HRM system (Codeigniter 3)

06/2023 - Present

Customer

AlphaECC - Southern Petroleum Construction Joint Stock

Company

Team size 6 member

#### DESCRIPTION

Manage organization and data for approximately 2000 employees, including timekeeping, leave management, and reporting and payroll.

#### TASK:

- · Communicate with customers, take requests and execute requests
- Optimize code and improve query performance
- Perform all reports on hours, personnel and payroll
- Analyze, calculate and display employee working hours including holidays, Sundays and overtime. Then adjust base pay or hourly rate accordingly

TECHNOLOGY: HTML, CSS, JavaScript (jQuery), PHP(CodeIgniter 3), MySQL

LINK: https://hrm.alpha-ecc.com/

## Website selling fully functional watches (Laravel)

01/2023 - 05/2023

Graduation project 8 points

Team size 4 member

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Develop an e-commerce platform with functions such as purchasing, commenting, account management, registration, login, changing page layout and sending emails.

ROLE: Developer

TECHNOLOGY: HTML, CSS, JS (Jquery) - PHP (Laravel, Livewire) - MYSQL

LINK: https:://swatch.linhgv.name.vn

# Website selling clean food with basic functions (PHP core)

01/2022 - 4/2022

Subject project 1 8.5 points

Team size 5 member

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Develop a website selling clean food with functions such as purchasing, commenting, registering, logging in and sending emails.

ROLE: Developer

TECHNOLOGY: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL

LINK: https://github.com/gianglinhg/thucphamsach

#### Movie website (Restful API)

04/2023 - Present

Personal project

#### **DESCRIPTION**

Develop a movie viewing platform with functions such as movie management, movie viewing, registration, login, movie crawler, statistics and email sending.

**ROLE**: Fullstack Developer

TECHNOLOGY: Laravel, Vuejs, Antdv, TailwindCss, MariaDB

## Website selling basic functional clothes (Laravel)

01/2023 - 05/2023

Personal project

#### DESCRIPTION

Develop an e-commerce platform with functions such as purchasing, commenting, account management, registration, login, changing page layout and sending emails.

**ROLE**: Developer

TECHNOLOGY: HTML, CSS, JS (Jquery) - PHP (Laravel, Livewire) - MYSQL

LINK: https://github.com/gianglinhg/linhg\_shop\_livewire